

# - Dylan Cole -

8

Atlanta, Georgia

dylan1217@mindspring.com

(404) 977-3555

## **Professional Summary**

Hardworking and motivated student with solid experience working in multiple professional corporate environments. Disciplined with time management and reliable at completing tasks proficiently. Experienced at working in a team environment to collaborate on complex software projects.

#### **Education**

# Etowah High School (Advanced Placement Courses)

Woodstock, GA Class of 2021

Kennesaw State University (Dual Enrollment toward Computer Science College Credits)

Kennesaw, GA 2020-2021

# Louisiana State University (Computer Science Major)

Baton Rouge, LA 2021-Present Graduating Dec 2024 GPA 3.21

#### **Relevant Coursework**

- CSC 1350, 1351 (Computer Science I and II)
- CSC 2259 (Discrete Structures)
- CSC 3102 (Advanced Data Structures & Algorithm Analysis)
- CSC 4402 (Introduction to Database Management Systems)

#### Software

- Java
- C
- C++
- HTML
- CSS
- SQL - AutoCAD
- GIS
- Maya 2024
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Proficient in Digital Animation

### **Work Experience**

Threadkore, LLC Midland, GA (May 2024 – August 2024)

Interned as part of the development and Implementation team at the startup Threadkore. The company helps businesses manage all aspects of homebuilding and construction with a variety of technological tools helping to streamline communication and increase efficiency. Responsibilities included creating and executing SQL queries in the company database to retrieve information as well as using the SQL queries to create reports for homebuilders to use for information retrieval. Other projects included optimizing the website layout for computer and mobile use to improve user usability as well as locating and reporting bugs in the application. This internship provided experience relevant to the computer science industry and helped to improve my efficiency as a programmer. Additionally, this role gave experience managing numerous projects and interacting on collaborative projects with other programmers.

Ramboll Americas Engineering Solutions, Inc. Baton Rouge, Louisiana (March 2023 - Sep 2023) Engineering Intern for an international environmental consulting company. Worked for the Restore Louisiana Program assessing environmental damage to residential structures and verifying eligibility for federal relief funds. Reported information on environmental hazards using a field tablet to survey, photo-document, and analyze potential environmental hazards and their geographical location. The work required extensive travel across various parishes throughout Louisiana. The internship provided experience problem-solving with colleagues and interacting with Louisiana's residents who were affected by environmental disasters.

#### Bennett Thrasher

Atlanta, Georgia (May 2021 - Aug 2021)

Worked as an information technology intern at a professional business consulting and accounting firm. Duties included user and systems data collection and server maintenance. Additional responsibilities included reporting and tracking technology supplies, tracking inventory, and replacing faulty equipment. Also responsible for imaging new laptops with updated software platforms. The role required the ability to handle multiple tasks simultaneously and encouraged collaboration with colleagues to problem solve.

### **Relevant Academic Projects**

"Terminal Fit" (C++, SQL)

Developed a workout application for users to create an account and enter biometric data. Users could then update their profile with new information to document weekly progress. Application also included features to recommend workout routines and diet plans based off user desired goals.

#### Car Rental Agency Database (SQL, HTML, Java)

Created a database for Enterprise Car Rental to manage relevant information for the car rental agency. Tasks included creating and modifying entity relationship diagrams, creating search queries to find relevant information stored within the database, and using SQL to create appointments, store customer data, and modify existing reservations.